The heart wants to sit under the blanket and eat peanuts The
heart wants to sit in front of the fireplace and chat The heart
wants to have potato parathas smeared with desi ghee,
straight from the pan to the plate
Then fill the tub with hot water and sit in it for hours
[Music]
Wake up in the morning and then go to sleep
Sip tea in front of the campfire
[Music]
Only barfi should be eaten throughout the year
[Music] The
heart wants this heart to be defeated again today The
promise of showing your daughter that you are fit should be fulfilled today
You keep your promises, we will keep ours
Health and wellness solutions firm
ICICI Lambard takes care of not only yours but
also your wellness
ICICI Lumbard keeps its promises